A group of very cold tourists are sitting in a cafe in Old Quebec drinking hot coffee
to try to warm up.
The temperature is 32 degrees below freezing.
The windows are covered with steam from the heat inside.
Outside, snow covers the streets and is piled up along the sidewalks.
The music and lights of the Carnival continue,
but after a whole day of watching parades,
riding in horse carriages and listening to the music,
their feet are freezing and their noses are red.
Everyone who comes must be prepared to keep moving,
as it is too cold to stand and watch for long.
Early in the morning, you can watch the snowboarding competitions on the hill overlooking the river.
Competitors speed down the track and through the air as though they could fly.
One of the favourite events is the dog-sled race,
in which teams of about six husky dogs pull long sleds at great speeds along a snowy track.
One person runs behind the sled,
shouting to the dogs to encourage them.
The sound of the dogs barking,
the calls of the drivers and the shouts of the crowd make an exciting Northern experience.
The dogs are beautiful strong animals,
with long, thick fur and many with blue eyes.
It is amazing how warm these ice houses can be!
Late in the evening, you can go to the snow palace,
where Bonhomme the snowman is king,
and join the crowd.
You can dance outside to the music of a band,
who are all dressed in heavy clothes - even some of their instruments are dressed up
for winter.
You might join the snowmobile races - or maybe you should just sleep in!